https://www.imsociety.org/privacy_policy.php

Menopause Health Tracker App
Member Login
Forgot Password
Search:
10th December 2020 -
IMS is looking to fill the position of Scientific Editor to coordinate and deliver the...Read More
8th December 2020 -
The seventh in the series of IMS Webinars entitled "Dealing with a big issue - weight gain at...Read More
Melbourne 2020
Subscribe to newsletter
Privacy Policy
The International Menopause Society respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal data.
Purpose of this privacy notice
This privacy notice applies when you visit our website (www.imsociety.org). It also applies where you are a member of the IMS (past or present), a registered user of our website or contacting us for any other purposes.
For example, this includes: when you apply to join the IMS, register with our website, sign up to our newsletter, register for IMS events, conferences including subscribing to updates ,or contact the IMS for any other purpose (including via social media).
Our website and products and services are not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.
It is important that you read this privacy notice together with any other privacy notice or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This privacy notice supplements the other notices and is not intended to override them.
Third-party links
Our website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements.
When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy notice of every website you visit (for example to see how they use your information and to find out how to opt out, or delete, such information).
Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data).
We may collect and use,
different kinds of personal data about you which we have grouped together as follows:
Identity Data - includes first name, maiden name, last name, gender.
Contact Data - includes postal and billing address, email address, telephone number and photos .
Transaction Data - includes details about payments to and from you and other details of products and services you have purchased and used from us.
Technical Data - includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this website.
Profile Data - includes your ID and password.
We have additional obligations to treat sensitive personal information with appropriate care, taking into account the nature of that information. The best way to restrict the processing of your sensitive personal data is not to give it to us unless it is necessary for the services you are obtaining from us.
The information you provide to us is confidential and protected by law. The confidentiality of personal information is a top priority for the IMS. Your personal information is not shared with any external organisation, government department, local council, or marketing company. The information collected will be used solely for official purposes. Analysis of the data will not be used in any way that allows individuals to be identified.
Contact details
Our registered office is
International Menopause Society
Rebecca Cheshire, IMS CEO
PO Box 751, Truro, Cornwall TR2 4WD UK
Tel: +44 1726 884 221
E-mail: rebecca.cheshire@imsociety.org
Quick Links
Tel: Please contact support@imsimpart.com for any help you may require accessing IMPART
E-mail: rebecca.cheshire@imsociety.org
© 2015.
International Menopause Society | All Rights Reserved
